♪ ♪
- SquarePants and Star
Babysitting?
- 方裤和星星
保姆？
Oh, please.
哦，拜托。
What do you two nitwits know
about taking care of babies?
你们两个白痴懂什么
关于照顾婴儿？
- Just watch.
- 就看吧。
- Huh?
- 啊？
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
- Safety pin.
- 安全别针。
Ointment.
软膏。
- Doo-doo.
- 嘟嘟。
[cries]
[哭声]
[sucks]
[糟透了]
- Aw, such a good
wittle squiddy.
- 噢，这么好
鱿鱼。
- No one in their right mind
- 没有人头脑正常
would ever hire you
as babysitters.
会雇用你
作为保姆。
- Yoo-hoo!
Babysitters!
- 哟吼！
保姆们！
I could use
some babysitters here.
我可以用
这里有一些保姆。
- Oh, boy!
- 哦，孩子！
[bang]
[砰]
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
[groans]
[呻吟]
- SquarePants and Star
babysitters at your service.
- 方裤和星星
保姆为您服务。
- We sit on babies.
- 我们坐在婴儿身上。
- Not literally.
- 不是字面上的意思。
- Yeah, not in Italy.
- 是的，不是在意大利。
- Now you kids behave,
and listen to the babysitters.
- 现在你们孩子们表现得好，
并听保姆的话。
Bye, now.
再见了。
- Bye.
- 再见。
[overlapping chatter]
[重叠的喋喋不休]
- Whoa!
- 哇！
A whole legion
of little darlings.
整个军团
小宝贝们。
All right, Patrick.
好吧，帕特里克。
You take the east flank,
I'll take the west,
你占据东翼，
我要向西走，
and we'll try to establish
a nap zone in the middle.
我们将尝试建立
中间有一个午睡区。
- [laughs]
- [笑]
These babies
are no match for my...
这些婴儿
都配不上我的...
Toddler Style.
幼儿风格。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[continues grunting]
[继续咕哝]
[groans]
[呻吟]
[babies crying]
[婴儿哭声]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[babies gasp]
[婴儿喘气]
[babies giggling]
[婴儿咯咯笑]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
[hollering]
[喊叫]
[babies crying]
[婴儿哭声]
[babies screaming]
[婴儿尖叫声]
[chewing]
[咀嚼]
- [babbling]
- [胡言乱语]
- [panicked grunts]
- [惊慌的咕哝声]
[continues babbling]
[继续胡言乱语]
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
- [chattering]
- [喋喋不休]
- [exhales]
- [呼气]
[babies crying]
[婴儿哭声]
[babies cheering]
[宝宝们欢呼]
[whistles]
[口哨声]
Bring her down!
把她拉下来！
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
[vacuum hums]
[真空嗡嗡声]
[babies murmuring]
[婴儿低语]
[babies babbling]
[婴儿牙牙学语]
- Yeah.
- 是的。
both: Shh!
两人：嘘！
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
- And they all lived
happily ever after
- 他们都活着
从此幸福快乐
inside an oyster shell.
在牡蛎壳里面。
- Aww.
- 哇。
Thank you,
SquarePants and Star.
谢谢你，
方裤和星星。
- Babysitters!
- 保姆！
- Skinny or chunky!
Clean or funky!
- 瘦或矮胖！
干净或时髦！
- We won't get paid
if your kid's mislaid.
- 我们不会得到报酬
如果您的孩子丢失了。
- Oh, boys.
Right here.
- 哦，孩子们。
就在这里。
Oh, I could use a babysitter.
哦，我可以请个保姆。
- Ooh!
- Hey!
- 哦！
- 嘿！
While you go out
and dance and revel...
当你外出时
跳舞、狂欢……
- We will watch
your little devil.
- 我们会观看
你的小恶魔。
- Yes!
- 是的！
Ooh, thank you.
哦，谢谢你。
Thank you.
谢谢。
- Hey, where's the baby?
- 嘿，宝宝在哪儿？
- She's inside!
- 她在里面！
I'm free, I'm free.
我自由了，我自由了。
[cackles]
[咯咯笑]
- Hm.
- 嗯。
[confused mutters]
[困惑的嘀咕]
- Baby.
- 婴儿。
Baby?
婴儿？
- Is this the baby?
- 这是婴儿吗？
- No, I don't think so.
- 不，我不这么认为。
- Huh.
Ooh.
- 嗯。
哦。
This looks like
a nice baby girl.
这看起来像
一个漂亮的女婴。
- She's nice,
but she's not a baby.
- 她人很好，
但她不是婴儿。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
Aww, I found the baby.
哇哦，我找到宝宝了。
[scary music]
[恐怖音乐]
- [yelps]
- [尖叫声]
It's the ugliest baby
I've ever seen.
这是最丑的宝宝
我曾经见过。
- Patrick, all babies
are beautiful.
- 帕特里克，所有的宝宝
很漂亮。
Even the ugly ones.
即使是丑陋的。
Hey, we don't know
what the baby's name is.
嘿，我们不知道
宝宝的名字是什么。
- She looks like she's
been in the tub too long.
- 她看起来就像是
在浴缸里呆得太久了。
Let's call her Baby Prunes.
我们就叫她小李子吧。
- What a pretty name.
Little Baby Prunes.
- 多么漂亮的名字啊。
小李子宝宝。
[laughing]
[笑]
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
Who are you?
Where's Lazy Mary?
你是谁？
懒惰玛丽在哪里？
- The baby can talk!
- 宝宝会说话了！
- Help, help!
It's a robbery!
- 救命，救命！
这是抢劫！
- No, Patrick.
- 不，帕特里克。
Baby Prunes is just mimicking
what she's heard.
小李子只是在模仿
她听到了什么。
It's just baby talk.
She's babbling.
这只是儿戏而已。
她在胡言乱语。
- I'm not babbling,
you boneheads.
-我不是胡言乱语
你们这些笨蛋。
- Din-din time.
- 喧闹时间。
Here comes the airplane.
飞机来了。
[mimicking train]
【模仿火车】
[gulps]
[吞咽]
Yum.
嗯。
Playtime!
玩耍时间！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Kids love to build things
with blocks.
孩子们喜欢建造东西
与块。
- Heh. Oh, I'll build
something all right...
- 呵呵。哦，我会建造
没事...
[harmonica music]
[口琴音乐]
- Whoa, Patrick,
we've been playing in here
- 哇，帕特里克，
我们一直在这里玩
for three hours.
Better check on Baby Prunes.
三个小时。
最好检查一下小西梅。
You know what's
the best part of playing jail?
你知道是什么
玩监狱最好的部分是什么？
- No.
- Jail break!
- 不。
- 越狱！
- Jail break!
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- I gotta pick this lock
and get outta here.
- 我得撬开这把锁
离开这里。
- Oh, there you are.
- 哦，你来了。
Come on, come on.
来吧，来吧。
- Nap time.
- 午睡时间。
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
Put me down,
you yellow scouring pad!
把我放下来，
你这个黄色百洁布！
Unhand me!
松开我！
No.
不。
Get me out of here.
带我离开这里。
[mumbling]
[咕哝]
- [vocalizing]
- [发声]
- [grumbling]
- [抱怨]
- Oh, who's a colicky baby?
- 哦，谁是绞痛婴儿？
It's you.
Coochie coochie coo!
是你。
咕咕咕咕！
I'll go up and prepare a bath
我上去准备洗澡
for Baby Prunes
for when she wakes up.
适合小李子
当她醒来时。
- Okay, while you're doing
that, I'll just space out.
- 好吧，当你做的时候
那我就出去一下。
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Hm.
Strange.
- 嗯。
奇怪的。
There don't seem to be
any baby items in here.
好像没有
这里有任何婴儿用品。
Okay, pills, pills, dentures,
more pills, hemorrhoid cream.
好吧，药丸，药丸，假牙，
多吃药，痔疮膏。
Ew.
呃。
Happy birthday to mother
on her 137th birthday.
祝妈妈生日快乐
在她 137 岁生日那天。
Aww.
哇。
[gasps]
137th birthday?
[喘气]
137 岁生日？
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
Oh, Baby Prunes isn't a baby!
She's an old lady!
哦，梅干宝宝不是婴儿！
她是个老太太了！
- [snarling]
- [咆哮]
Ah, come on.
啊，来吧。
- [mumbling]
- [咕哝]
Is that a puppy I hear?
我听到的是一只小狗吗？
I didn't know they had a puppy.
我不知道他们有一只小狗。
What is it, puppy?
这是什么，小狗？
You want to go out?
你想出去吗？
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
Arf!
Arf, arf!
阿尔夫！
阿尔夫，阿尔夫！
- Here you go, puppy.
- 给你，小狗。
- So long, sucker!
- 再见，笨蛋！
[laughs]
[笑]
[barks]
[吠叫]
- The puppy knows
baby talk, too.
- 小狗知道
儿语也是。
- Patrick, she's not a baby!
- 帕特里克，她不是婴儿！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Where's Baby Prunes?
小李子在哪里？
- I don't know.
I just let the puppy out.
- 我不知道。
我刚刚把小狗放了出来。
- That was no puppy.
That was an old lady.
- 那不是小狗。
那是一位老太太。
An old lady that we're
responsible for.
我们是一位老太太
负责。
both: [yelling]
两人：[大喊]
- If you were an old lady,
where would you go?
- 如果你是一位老太太，
你会去哪里？
- I don't know.
Back in time?
- 我不知道。
回到过去？
- What about a sewing circle?
- 缝纫圈怎么样？
- Yes, a sewing circle
back in time.
- 是的，一个缝纫圈
回到过去。
[yelling]
[大喊]
- Come on.
- 快点。
[boom]
[繁荣]
Old Lady Prunes?
老太太李子？
all: Huh?
全体：啊？
- You seen a baby
that's really an old lady?
- 你看到了一个婴儿
这真的是个老太太吗？
- Oh, look, they have schmutz
on their faces.
- 哦，看，他们有坏脾气
在他们的脸上。
[gurgling]
[淙淙]
[hocking]
[霍克]
- No, not that.
- 不，不是那样。
- [whimpering]
- [呜咽]
[overlapping chatter]
[重叠的喋喋不休]
- Ah! Where's
Baby Old Lady Prunes?
- 啊！在哪里
宝贝老太太李子？
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
all: Yeah!
全体：是啊！
- Yee-haw!
Lava-bunga!
- 哎呀！
熔岩花！
- Ahh!
- 啊！
- I'm okay!
- 我没事！
- [laughs]
- [笑]
both: Yeah!
两人：是啊！
- Ah! What are you doing?
You don't have a parachute.
- 啊！你在干什么？
你没有降落伞。
- Parachutes are for babies.
- 降落伞是给婴儿用的。
[laughs]
[笑]
[continues laughing]
[继续笑]
Oh, yeah!
哦，是啊！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[laughs]
[笑]
- Prunes!
- 李子！
- Old Lady Prunes!
- 老太太李子！
- Old Lady Baby Prunes!
- 老太太婴儿李子！
[bell ringing]
[铃声响起]
[punching]
[冲孔]
- [yelling]
- [大喊]
- Huh?
- 啊？
[all grunt]
[全都咕哝]
- Well, if it isn't
my two babysitters.
- 好吧，如果不是的话
我的两个保姆。
You humiliated me.
你羞辱了我。
- Prunes, you're alive.
- 梅子，你还活着。
- And still talking baby talk.
- 还在说儿语。
- Why I oughtta...
- 为什么我应该...
both: [screaming]
两人：[尖叫]
- Aww. Pruny wants to play.
Nice old lady.
- 哇。普鲁尼想玩。
好一个老太太。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- [laughs]
- [笑]
[pounding]
[重击]
- [murmuring]
- [低语]
[snoring]
[打鼾]
- Aww.
- 哇。
Her boxing tuckered her out.
她的拳击让她筋疲力尽。
[thud]
[砰]
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
- Aww.
- 哇。
both: Shh.
两人：嘘。
- Ahh.
Another job well done.
- 啊。
另一项工作做得很好。
[sniffs]
[嗅嗅]
Uh, Patrick, I think
she needs to be changed.
呃，帕特里克，我想
她需要改变。
- No, that's me.
- 不，那是我。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪